Bind Ferri

Contact

Phone

+38349519310

Email

bindferri@gmail.com

Additional Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- PHP
- Wordpress
- Laravel(Learning)
- Java(Basic)

Professional Summary

My name is Bind Ferri , 24 years old.Born and raised in Prishtina , Kosovo.Very friendly person , communicative , funny and positive.Jobs where teamwork is necessary , positivity is crucial to make it work.Atmosphere at work is another crucial point , that's where i can help alot.Able to work under high pressure and deadlines.I'm very passionate programmer whos is eager to learn more and more every day and i'm very hungry for success. I like to write clean,organised code (ex. OOP programming) and stay updated with new trends and new programming languages.

Work Experience

2018 - 2019

Co-Owner of a Gaming Center

In 2018 I was a Co-Owner of a Gaming Center that lasted for a year. We started the business with 25 gaming pcs and had a really good start , but because of the pandemic situation everything went upside down , and in 2019 we closed the business.

2019 - Ongoing

Creator of a Youtube Channel

In 2019, in pandemic time when we all were isolated for around 3 months, everyone spent alot of time on social media and other internet platforms. So I had an idea of creating a Gaming Youtube Channel, which actually turned out to be a great idea. My channel is still growing and I am really happy that during isolation I did something successful

Programming

I don't have any work experience in programming yet. But I Have a lot of local projects and online courses that I have completed.

You can check my projects on: www.github.com/bindferri

Education

2003 - 2012

"Ismail Qemali", Prishtine

Elementary School

2012 - 2015

"Sami Frasheri", Prishtine

High School

2015

UBT - Computer Science and Engeneering , Prishtine

Bachelor

2006 - 2015

"Oxford Studio", Prishtine

English Language

Online Courses

The Ultimate HTML/CSS Mastery Series - Mosh Hamedani The Ultimate Java Mastery Series - Mosh Hamedani JavaScript Basics for Beginners - Mosh Hamedani Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS - Jonas Schmedtmann

The Complete JavaScript Course 2022: From Zero to Expert! - Jonas Schmedtmann

PHP OOP: Object Oriented Programming for beginners + Project - Edwin Diaz

PHP for Beginners - Become a PHP Master - CMS Project - Edwin Diaz Object Oriented PHP & MVC - Brad Traversy

Become a WordPress Developer: Unlocking Power With Code - Brad Schiff

Languages

Albanian — Mother Tongue

English — C1